shopbmwusa.com 2016-03-14

# ShopBMWUSA.com: Help

The information below provides an overview of our privacy policy. Please use the links in the menu bar to the left to access further details.

Our Promise to You  
We appreciate the trust you place in BMW and would not want to jeopardize your trust in any way. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting the security of your personal information. Rest assured that we will not rent or sell your personal information to anyone.

BMW works with retailers and contracted business partners to provide you with products and services and to give you the best ownership experience possible. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards designed to protect your personal information. We will address your privacy-related questions or concerns.

Our Commitment to Privacy

What information does BMW collect?  
As part of providing you with our products and services, we obtain 'personal information' about you, such as your name, address, email and phone number, when you submit such information to us. We also may obtain such information from third parties. 'Personal information' means information that identifies you or could reasonably be used to identify you. We also may collect other information about your visits to our site without you actively submitting such information. This information may include, for example, your browser type and language, your operating system, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the URLs of sites you visited before and after visiting our site, the web search that landed you on our site, and web pages and advertisements you view and links you click on within our site.

How does BMW use my personal information?  
Our primary goal in collecting personal information from you is to facilitate efficient transactions and provide you with information regarding relevant products and services. BMW will not do anything to jeopardize your trust, including renting or selling your personal information.

What information does BMW share?  
We share personal information with members of the BMW Group, to assist us in providing offers for products or services that may be of interest to you. Members of the BMW Group include, BMW of North America, BMW Financial Services, BMW Bank of North America, and BMW Insurance Agency. We share personal information with non-affiliated companies that provide services on our behalf. All of these companies are contractually obligated to keep the personal information that we provide to them confidential and to use such information only to provide the services we ask them to perform. We also share personal information with non-affiliated companies that market our products and services, such as our retail centers who are distinct entities and have their own privacy policies.

Is my personal information secure?  
We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards designed to protect personal information. We also employ encryption technologies and user authentication procedures that are designed to keep your data secure. We limit access to personal information to authorized personnel and contractors who need access to perform their job and are contractually required to keep your information secure.

How am I updated on BMW's privacy policy?  
As business conditions change, we will update this policy to reflect changes in our business practices. We will post revisions to our policy on our web site.

Questions and Comments  
Please feel free to send your privacy-related comments or questions to privacy@bmwusa.com or write: BMW of North America, Privacy Office, PO Box 1227, Westwood NJ 07675-1227. You may also call Customer Relations at 800-831-1117, Prompt 'Customer Service Vehicle.' Customer telephone calls may be recorded to protect you and our staff.

Platform Use Restrictions  
You may use the Content only for your own non-commercial use to participate in the Platform or to place an order or purchase BMW products. You agree not to change or delete any ownership notices from materials downloaded or printed from the Platform. You agree not to modify, copy, translate, broadcast, perform, display, distribute, frame, reproduce, republish, download, display, post, transmit or sell any Intellectual Property or Content appearing on the Platform, including User Generated Content (defined below), without BMW's prior written consent, unless it is your own User Generated Content that you legally post on the Platform. You agree not to use any data mining, robots, scraping or similar data gathering methods. Nothing in these Terms of Use shall be interpreted as granting any license of intellectual property rights to you.

Thank you for your continued interest in BMW.
